<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="ls_header">
		<text>AnomaLite</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_number">
		<text>Tip #</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_1">
		<text>Avoid encumbrance, it will get you killed. Remember to periodically sell those extra items you don't need, or stash them for future use. Backpacks bought from traders can be used as stashes.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_2">
		<text>Hunting mutants will net you some of their parts. Additionally, you'll get meat that you can cook if you're low on cash. Just have around something to reduce radiation after such a meal.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_3">
		<text>Basic, advanced, and expert toolkits are required by many mechanics in order to perform certain upgrades on weapons and outfits. Such items can often be found in stashes received as rewards for completing tasks.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_4">
		<text>Sleep deprivation is an optional feature where the passage of time and using consumables will gradually drain the player - eventually requiring them to rest when prompted. Failing to do so may have dire consequences.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_5">
		<text>Helicopter patrols are an optional feature with powerful effects on the Zone. When engaged in combat, members of the helicopter's faction may often call on it for air support to help destroy attacking or defending forces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_6">
		<text>Ironman mode gives a true sense of mortality. When the player has lost all their lives, all saves for that specific character are deleted and can never be restored. Pick your faction and starting location wisely.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_7">
		<text>It's best to familiarise yourself with sewing kits, gun oil and glue tubes - these items can help keep your gear pristine in the field for much longer. Full repair kits are more potent, but also rarer, heavier and costlier.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_8">
		<text>Backpacks can be bought or found and then used to create a custom stash. Stashes created by the player are never de-spawned nor are they ever looted by other stalkers. They are permanent until all items are removed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_9">
		<text>Sleeping bags are a great way to rest in the Zone if you are unable to find a decent bed to sleep in. They can be purchased from most major traders or potentially found in another stalker's stash.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_10">
		<text>Tools can be often found in indutrial areas. Rostok has been throughoutly searched many times so don't expect to find anything there. Instead look around harder to reach places such as Yantar factory or newly discovered industrial complex near Cordon.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
